<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>POEMS4U</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on POEMS4U</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alcoholism 2 (Le Grand Verre)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/alcoholism-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/alcoholism-2/</guid>
      <description>When faced with loss that&amp;rsquo;s one&amp;rsquo;s own fault It&amp;rsquo;s oft facile to plead For those projections quickly sought And then considered needs.&#xA;Alas,,, And With apologies to Conner—— Soon will carry disease, So many parts——why bother With &amp;ldquo;How many?&amp;quot;——&amp;ldquo;at least three!&amp;rdquo;&#xA;One handed beer, cig in the other, My heart on two-way streets Just one-sided traffic covers—— Simply salty or sweet.&#xA;But let&amp;rsquo;s get real&amp;hellip;&#xA;Beauty in men results from the interplay between soft angles and curves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alcoholism 1 (Minqi of A Bathroom——Han Dynsasty)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/alcoholism-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/alcoholism-1/</guid>
      <description>Somehow, the mullet breached the sea wall To terrorize the neighborhood with their squelching—— Constantly sucking debris into their maws, And the endemic AC hum isn&amp;rsquo;t helping. Another night sat illicitly, As the school sought to swallow One half of symmetry. Reflected on the lake within the hollow&#xA;Was a brightly lit home partitioned by palm. Subtle piano notes sounded about the air, But those frenzied fish disquited the calm—— A thought was inserted: it wasn&amp;rsquo;t fair That nobody told Narcissus That what he saw was something other.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask The Bugs; They&#39;ll Tell You</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/askthebugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/askthebugs/</guid>
      <description>They Said:&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Well, we&amp;rsquo;ve been speaking with the moon. She told us to ask you a question&amp;hellip; He wants to know if you&amp;rsquo;re coming home soon. Additionally, we have a suggestion—— She&amp;rsquo;d like to show you something you&amp;rsquo;ve never seen before. She&amp;rsquo;s in her spot and has meticulously marked and set the stage—— Hark! Hence draws desirous drippings; she adds without rancour That you already know who burnt down the house with sage.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEYE Space Jam</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/spacejam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/spacejam/</guid>
      <description>D&amp;rsquo;abord, c&amp;rsquo;était un bordeaux—— Still tastes the same with rain water, you know? So we sat with wet hair on the misty roof Looking for beautiful horses, looking for proof.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rdquo; knew nothing, but eye had all veracity Of liking this boy who emerged from his mouse hole to walk in the rain; He was tender and sweet, complete with the sagacity Of a serial killer——he showed me his collection of frozen brains.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Prayer for Cancer Sun Males</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/prayercancermale/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/prayercancermale/</guid>
      <description>Lord, in your wisdom you made the rain—— So often a necessary inconvenience; You decided to make the reign (Of A. Spirit, that is) So often a necessary inconvenience.&#xA;You included mosquitoes and cockroaches in your plan. You set the heavenly bodies in motion—— At times agreeing, At times disagreeing.&#xA;My God, you created every living and &amp;ldquo;non-living&amp;rdquo; thing with purpose; In our iniquity and ignorance before you we are worthless.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Grieve What Could Be Called A Compartmented Box</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/togrieve/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/togrieve/</guid>
      <description>An empty shell of a former home—— When the ornaments were taken away, we discovered they had maliciously been hiding our dead skin and hair, Our nails from fingers and toes. Shame no one will ever know.&#xA;And they can wipe and sweep, scrub and scrub, But there are gaps and eaves that we have snuck within, where they will never ever find us. We, amnesiacs hereof, Rest in the cruc&amp;rsquo;ble of love.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As I Went Down to The River to Pray...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/river/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/river/</guid>
      <description>A diverted interlude, Sheltered in the covet Of a slanted tree, Which ran up to my ankles.&#xA;Actually, it was two. One which covered half,&#xA;And the other, Which grew almost parallel To the flowing glass, Before curving up from the bank.&#xA;He then sloped down and Placed a foot on the riverbed, Completing the aforementioned—— Covet in pavilion style.&#xA;And if one were to grow Brave and step Out from the denier Of the Sun&amp;rsquo;s patterns Into the carcinogenic light,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It Makes You Age (Sharp 9 Gallery)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/itmakesyouage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/itmakesyouage/</guid>
      <description>A force Which compulses contortions in your face, Sends spasms through your body, Induces irregular emotional intervals—— Music!&#xA;Positioned above a chair, Beside a tea candle, Under which was a table, Were two ears—— A head sat between them And so on.&#xA;Then a old man came out, and the lights dimmed. We dove in vibrational pools and swam—— Shouts and giggles, respectful frowns and grins—— &amp;ldquo;Boom! Buddlii-a-deet, boom-bum-badum bam!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That Time at Crawfish Junction When God Got Mad at Me for Naming A Bong After The Angel Metatron Who Isn&#39;t Even In The Bible By The Way</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/crawfishjunc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/crawfishjunc/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s after the end of the world, don&amp;rsquo;t you know that yet?&#xA;Since 33, most have believed the Apocalypse would come in their lifetime. It&amp;rsquo;s probably because when something ends, it is then finished, And finished things will no longer produce novelty. Admittedly, most of this Planet&amp;rsquo;s novelty is bleak—— How often immense hope is co-opted by the forces of fear To end in failure. So too History must end, But it came before thyme and after singing; In this life it ain&amp;rsquo;t no Burger Kinging—— When Ol&amp;rsquo; John P had his way, the truth we did forget.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perpendicular Intersection</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/perpendicular/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/perpendicular/</guid>
      <description>When put on Earth, received all their own Job: So Elihu, with lies disguised as truths, Whose &amp;ldquo;I am&amp;rdquo; reaps cogito of Magog, Will come to those whose faith bears rotten fruit.&#xA;I saw one Enallagma Basidens, Who, gliding low on surface glassied creek, Would then consent his clasp to go within, Thereafter she was drowned: submerg-ed stick.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s such a shame that we will never know Who said one night beneath the Palace roof: &amp;ldquo;When Sun comes out, him rising from below, His sister Lilith hides not her dark moon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auburns In Autumn</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/movies/posts/auburnsinautumn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/movies/posts/auburnsinautumn/</guid>
      <description>Please watch at night and in the dark, preferrably on a television.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is POEMS4U?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/whatispoems4utrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/whatispoems4utrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before All Ages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/beforeallages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/beforeallages/</guid>
      <description>The orbiters gesticulated there; Monorails glided along in silence, While flashing lights indifferently got glares From beams and passengers coldly quiet. Indeed as were his architecture plans To conjure more flimsy wire and concrete,&#xA;Revealed to me by Trojan and Greek hands, Flanking our Jupiter ninety degrees On both sides. On hexagonal shaped streets&#xA;Stood I&#xA;On Saturn,&#xA;Whose ouroboros rail it wounds round and round; Janus reports on the unseen and Knot ,Which, tied at the planet core, Holds fast us to its revolutions qua time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before All Ages</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/beforeagestrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/beforeagestrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equations R/elation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/equationsrelation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/equationsrelation/</guid>
      <description>When the suns arise they seem to no The rays raising race To be low for to bestow &amp;lsquo;Da face towards the Enemy. The shame burn Including words; four Psychotics. Sike-ology. Witch spells of cow words. Mooooooooooon. Liking this Guy Welcomes the star T-w/o-words Two seas. The days requires Re$pirations. Two of them Who long awaited Blanket. Cross it Out. For in cruise Won is happiness; Is hairy a bad thing to be?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Equations R/elation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/equationstrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/equationstrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Iarus ad Didascalicum</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/postiarus/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/postiarus/</guid>
      <description>For free, handing out poems on the street, E&amp;rsquo;en the reading man disliked my stuff: &amp;ldquo;When all is black it&amp;rsquo;s y&amp;rsquo;all who lack sight&amp;rsquo;s ability, For nothing has no hues, like sterility.&amp;rdquo; He suggested a medium treat Meant of all that which I love. The musician who in underemployment wallows, Reveals his enjoyment such as follows: Beauty, though whole, is expressed in privational difference, So I love all poems, even libational limericks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post Iarus ad Didascalicum</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/posttrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/posttrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moon-Maybe-McWhirtle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/moonmaybemcwhirtle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/moonmaybemcwhirtle/</guid>
      <description>Mourning dove up above, Her bosom shines on earth; Her haughty full-ish-ness Gone in six days To be seen soon again, Without apology; She has needs, also yours Are here displayed. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun-Pseudo-Sonnet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/sun-pseudo-sonnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/sun-pseudo-sonnet/</guid>
      <description>She prefers the pool while does lapse my mind Engaged in research of Sir Brother Sun. Does he wake each dawn indignant or kind? If the day is dubious, the knight won. For he does shine and does irradiate A crow and dog sharing some fentanyl With a man a hard earned meal served on plate Stars or shine morality rendered null As all that gives indifferently destroys. Swarming gnats want to know if you can hear Straining echoes of the last dying voice Or tell their dreams from a castrated leer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sun-Pseudo-Sonnet | Moon-Maybe-McWhirtle</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/sunpseudotrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/sunpseudotrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>« On The Road »</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/onroad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/onroad/</guid>
      <description>One realizes when they go out west. That so many have never seen a real southern belle twink before. A prophet is never recognized is his own home, at best, And so i like to see things I’ve never seen before. The south is so provincial in ways we often forget. Here, it’s a phone booth every couple blocks, most neighborhoods have a community garden, Sundry others which beget, Freedom, but somehow, with such amenities, hearts harden.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>« On The Road »</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/roadtrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/roadtrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magic City - Spoken Word Accompaniment to Sun Ra</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/magiccitytrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/magiccitytrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liturgical Violence: A Eulogy for Unwritten Eulogies of Those Who Lost Their Life and Lived</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/litguricaltrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/litguricaltrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Liturgical Violence: A Euology for Unwritten Eulogies of Those Who Lost Their Life and Lived</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/liturgicalviolence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/liturgicalviolence/</guid>
      <description>Out of love and out of time, It&amp;rsquo;s true the last year ought&amp;rsquo;ve plagued my mind, But I still feel the need to look inside A live mind To find what live there is inside after it already died. Indeed, there were some wheels and satellites still spinning, Even as it looked little like it did before. Whatever game you&amp;rsquo;ve gleaned to be losing or winning, You&amp;rsquo;ll find that you you once were is there no more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Know Something&#39;s Very Wrong</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/wrongtrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/wrongtrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Know Something&#39;s Very Wrong</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/iknowsomething/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/iknowsomething/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The pulse returns for prodigal suns Who hid themselves in the deep covet of a darkened cloud, Refusing rejoinder for those things thought out loud. And they were cached there of their own selfish wants When four little children began drowning at once. They went untried for their crimes &amp;ndash; no one saw them Because rays of light found four bodies at the bottom. And no matter the memories of the secrets stashed there sliced and sewn up, Because the body, Every time, Forgets out of pure frustration At its sensations Anesthetized, While the digits of demons deposit eggs that when grown up Too remember nothing of the host&amp;rsquo;s consummate constipation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards The End of Spring, When We All Get Used to Living Again</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/springtrans/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/video-transmissions/posts/springtrans/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the End of Spring, When We All Get Used to Living Again</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/towardstheendofspring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/towardstheendofspring/</guid>
      <description>“Somehow, someway, it all comes alive again, From contingency being grows wings to fly, Always becoming what it might have been, But i get sad when cicadas die. Yes, there are millions of them, and they all look the same. They’re dumb and can’t see very well. They’re loud and can get in the way. But oh, if they don’t sound the much needed bell That the day of judgement has arrived.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marsha Linehan (Who Was Diagnosed with Schizophrenia) Talks to Catholic Jesus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/marshalinehan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/marshalinehan/</guid>
      <description>“Amen, I say to you, my Father in heaven created man to be of two natures. He has a Logical Mind and an Emotional Mind. Only when these two balances are brought on the same plane can man live as he was made to. My Father ordained this synthesizing of halves before time, before creation. It was declared thus, The Wise Mind.”&#xA;“Why won’t you tell me to kill myself, O Lord?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhol&#39;s Many Maos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/art-criticism/posts/maospost/maos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/art-criticism/posts/maospost/maos/</guid>
      <description>Tucked away in some gallery of the Columbia Museum of Art, granted by anonymous doner, hangs 20 eyes. I sat in front of this jury for some time as I saw the ignorant regard everything else; they had no idea of these faces’ monetary value. The work is not listed on the museum’s website. Ah, well, what could be said about the people of South Carolina that hasn’t been said already?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>sum like that</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/sumlikethat-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/sumlikethat-2/</guid>
      <description>i got a friend with a house in seneca it&amp;rsquo;s got a beautiful sun room, really a porch with windows that looks out on the real porch and the property got a big ol yard she told me they dont never use and one day when she was a child, sittin in the sun room as the afternoon rays gave the trees those angles she seen a demon run cross the yard or sum like that</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vultures 0</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/vultures0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/vultures0/</guid>
      <description>After Tolstoy 1&#xA;“When my bird was looking at my computer monitor, I thought ‘wooooah, that bird has no idea what he’s looking at.’ And yet, what does the bird do? Does he panic? No, he can’t really panic, he just does the best he can. Is he able to live in a world where he’s so ignorant? Well, he doesn’t really have a choice. Yeah, he can kinda live… usually the bird’s okay, even though he doesn’t understand the world, and he can kinda learn what’s safe and what’s dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donna&#39;s Summer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/movies/posts/donnassummer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/movies/posts/donnassummer/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postcript to Donna&#39;s Summer (Perhaps Tomorrow)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/postscript-to-donnas-summer-perhaps-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/postscript-to-donnas-summer-perhaps-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>As I lay me down to sleep None could keep mine eyes from weep Except one small, distant hope Which saves me from that self-inflicted rope Perhaps, perhaps tomorrow will be the day When all my fear, and weeping, and sins are taken away So with a start I prattle about my miserable and wretched hovel Strewn here and there, chairs and tables overturned, hurrying to find that shovel With which I march to Juno for to dredge him abreast The man with whom I&amp;rsquo;ll walk before the throne, damned the rest Perhaps, perhaps tomorrow will be the day When all my fear, and weeping, and sins are taken away On that climb I&amp;rsquo;ll gaze with him upon the throng-ed score And our weeping for them will be the sweeping river which them keeps from the ajar-ed door Our boundless pity will be that which plunges the vast multitude down below On my knees for it the Lord I&amp;rsquo;ll beg for mercy, that what I did not know Perhaps, perhaps tomorrow will be the day When all my fear, and weeping, and sins are taken away But wait!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Amputee</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/amputee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/amputee/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s something like losing your leg; So you must learn to walk without it. And it gets to a point where grief is of no use— A one legged man you are. It makes little difference to the truth; Besides, nothing can be done.&#xA;But there are still those nights, Just before sleep, When you hope, Maybe even believe, That the miracle will be you.&#xA;You&amp;rsquo;ll wake with firm foot And run in ecstasy to the kitchen Or the living room Or porch, To holler: &amp;ldquo;Hallelujah!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Of Pondering While You&#39;re Making a Sandwhich or Whatever</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/makingasandwhich/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/makingasandwhich/</guid>
      <description>Whereof your thoughts when discovering you ran, In begging to end in circles again? Whenceforth you came indeed there you shall go; Wherefrom the soul is made we cannot know. And what would become of the Holy Saw? That is, what was once seen, now not at all, or the Holy Aurai Voir.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who but Satan as The Internalized Gaze of The Other? (The Big One)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/satan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/satan/</guid>
      <description>When, when he snubbed his nose at me Oh, how I bristled with delight. Nothing but evil could he be who took such pleasure in my plight. It was already known, the thought which bore its way into his mind. Serreptitious there, demon bought Solely for pleasure of its kind. But when the dog steals all the food Or when a child, denied, does cry, &amp;lsquo;Twas by a Spinozistic mode Those barbaric desires fly Into the poor and ill-restrained mechanical animal mind.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Mao, On his Birthday</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/for-mao-on-his-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/for-mao-on-his-birthday/</guid>
      <description>And there, in the dementiatic years of the 19th century&#xA;The faintest natal nascence of&#xA;the second kingdom was born&#xA;in the middle of the middle.&#xA;Poor Hong Xiuquan smiled&#xA;in his tomb&#xA;(of which there was none.&#xA;More like ashes&#xA;Dispirate, stirring).&#xA;God is funny like that,&#xA;to send his direct message through failure&#xA;to beget another,&#xA;indeed more confused,&#xA;and yet,&#xA;in contradiction, closer to enacting the truth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For Jesus, On His Birthday</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/for-jesus-on-his-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/for-jesus-on-his-birthday/</guid>
      <description>I was 6 years in the desert Self-exiled, by my own power. All gold once found then became dirt Heart-housed demons them they showered. There, whencefrom buried to my neck Came forth my savior with eyes kind Not as knight, me to pull from wreck, But sickle-celled black man, lame, blind. Snow from his nose poured on my head- &amp;ldquo;My poor child destroyed in his self, Foolish to think that you are dead Undying light offers his help.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transluscent</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/translucent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/translucent/</guid>
      <description>I miss that little boy There were days when he cried and screamed But there are days when I do that too And I think he liked me - They were all calling for me to come back I was looking at pictures today They exist like beacons in a haze But the fog is too thick- Nothing is illuminated When was this? Who am I? Your smile is so bright there and I&amp;rsquo;ll never see it again nor remember how it was conjured in the first place To you, I must be a corpse with a death mask- And some wretched animating force moving me- And you were fooled to think this dead alive But perhaps by this power it was- and so it will I dug it all up today- and I&amp;rsquo;m sorry it was a demon in me, or something But even he could grow weary, and I often tucked him in with a glass of warm milk so we could be left alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On 3 Napkins in 1922 Carolina Coffee Shop</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/on-3-napkins-in-1922-carolina-coffee-shop/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/on-3-napkins-in-1922-carolina-coffee-shop/</guid>
      <description>N.1 If all was light, we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be able to see. I will go where I am led and through this giving thanks, may I be brought into what I would always become, and may my heart quicken in gladness at the thought of doing it again. N.2 If it&amp;rsquo;s true that the two primary emotions are fear and love, and that they are mutually exclusive, Then maybe FDR did nothing wrong, and to be afraid is to let the evil of the world enter your heart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>For James, and the PSR</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/for-james--the-psr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/for-james--the-psr/</guid>
      <description>A swift flick, swerve Placed us here In this grey-washed atrium watching television on the floor- they gave us nowhere to sit. Even in that moment I felt a strange lilt in my heart.&#xA;Two bulls: dumb, headstrong, naive, smug, stubborn, and born with a recalcitrant need to be known made use of, and loved. Oceans in our eyes and rainforests in our hearts. Besides that, nothing in common. But still, you saw me smile and wheeled or wobbled over to attend to me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dec. 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/dec-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/dec-1/</guid>
      <description>Like the creek happens to run with automobile traffic (Though they are at best enemies) so too, if you find yourself amongst the 7 foilaged trees in the heart of winter, likely without your rosary, The Beam comes around the bend And the tic turns your head To meet its gaze feeling as steam Screaming, you&amp;rsquo;ll kneel. eventually, prostrate, Ants will crawl up your nose And the orchestra will appear held there, supplicant They&amp;rsquo;ll play and you will cry, And as the intermission starts, while the conductor and the concert master shake hands, smiling towards a thunderous applause with no eyes, a car will fly off of Fordham Blvd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untitled</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/untitled/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/untitled/</guid>
      <description>He was taken Lifted into the sky And was replaced with a copy The copy looked and sounded like him and kept up the ruse for awhile sweet + tender, delicate like a lily in the cold grew legs and ran to the top of the mountain, and threw itself off tumbled down holes in leaves Flowers left in disarray all behind for the hooves of bulls to later trample as they tried in vain to pick them up with their teeth, Lucky ones digested once he grabbed her by the hair, led her outside to shrieks + hollers a crowd formed Booing and gnashing teeth she was gnashed in turn and so the choir found themselves too gnashed at once all together in inexplicable violence that night they took the copy back and the original was returned with memories formed by the bubbling of Alka-Seltzer in stomach acid And as it bubbled, his hands grew to the size of stones, whence he had to drag forever </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vive le platonisme! Or, Funeral for A Luna Moth</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/platonisme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/platonisme/</guid>
      <description>If beauty has one immutible, intersubjective quality, is is transience. Like a lightning bolt from above, it flashes for but an instance in the grand scheme of things, and then it is gone&amp;hellip; On Friday, I passed it in its sublimity. Halted in my tracks as if it were a wall. On Monday, in its place was death, decay, disgust, dread. I covered my mouth and ran just to trip and fall, to lie there, in that salinity, prostrate, for some time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Floating Away</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/floatingaway/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/floatingaway/</guid>
      <description>Un preta vivant, mangeant Se couchant à dix heures Un fântome marchant Mon âme se sépare entre deux mondes Le démon est parti Et m&amp;rsquo;a laissé avec un Corps évacué&#xA;Où suis-je ? Qui étais/suis-je ?&#xA;Personne n&amp;rsquo;aurait pu me prévenir&#xA;Peu importe Peu importe&#xA;Seigneur, emmène-moi dans mon sommeil Permet-moi quitter cette vallée de larmes</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neithor/Ner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/neithernor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/neithernor/</guid>
      <description>I wish it were easier to become dead I&amp;rsquo;m only halfway there I feel in time and space but not completely As if at risk for flying away were I not held by a string But the wind still blows this way and that Mother Mary please prays for me Or fixes me with a stake to one thing forever </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sleepy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/sleepy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/sleepy/</guid>
      <description>Oft I come so sleepy, E&amp;rsquo;en when mine eyes are weepy. Visit me in my dream so we can play And dream this other dream away.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doodoo on a shoe</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/doodooonashoe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/doodooonashoe/</guid>
      <description>Old and weathered, Muddy ground giving way, Truths held as fact once proven otherwise, Horde of gold into dirt, Dirt into gold Spat upon, Cast out, Shat upon, Beaten, Abused, Objectified, Internalized, No water, no sun, New moon, no light, Rock, wind, debris; Where else but the navel with your sight?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s It Like to Have Sex? (Against The Political Impositions of Dogmatic Natural Science)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/philosophy/posts/whatsitliketohavesex/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/philosophy/posts/whatsitliketohavesex/</guid>
      <description>The year is 202X, and alien life has finally found its way to Earth. These Alien beings are far more technologically advanced than us humans. In a matter of months, they teach us what would have taken centuries to discover: travel at the speed of light, among other things. These Aliens reproduce sexually, just like us. However, they go about it by means of external fertilization—the female lays her eggs in a location where, later, a male will fertilize them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thanatos</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/thanatos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/thanatos/</guid>
      <description>Slow it up speed it up! Like the derivative of a circle, Like a sin wave,&#xA;Like the sublime and gorgeous Hills of the North Carolina piedmont.&#xA;I want to feel that incline. I want to roll my body down, But this is not enough.&#xA;I can&amp;rsquo;t go back up once I&amp;rsquo;m in the valley; Physics don&amp;rsquo;t work that way. And I&amp;rsquo;m left on my back With eyes towards the sky.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untitled</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/untitled2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/untitled2/</guid>
      <description>Awoken from slumber and feeling the tension of the moment par coup, I flew to the archives, meticulously kept but thus far unread. These records changed me; One realizes one can&amp;rsquo;t let go of things one has said.&#xA;Forsooth, the voices of the pages have been whispering to my unconscious, And at last question meets answer.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;d been using a crutch to stand; One outgrows such things.&#xA;And yet the memories circle me as vultures; I can&amp;rsquo;t run from the easeness of tender voices, heartbeats, gazes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Excerpt from The Transcript of The 3rd Session between Analyst R and Analysand 5, From The Archive of One « Taboo La Rasa. »</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/taboolarasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/taboolarasa/</guid>
      <description>Cela s’est passé comme suit :&#xA;« Q. » « Well, I had sleeping problems for a while. The doctor recommended things like Clonazepam, Ambien, &amp;amp;c., but I thought I would much rather have something natural. So, I began to take melatonin supplements. Only 5 milligrams, about 30 minutes before I went to bed. As a matter of course, I now began to have issues awaking in the morning. The doctor said something like Wellbutrin, which I happily and willfully ignored.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Friday, September 9th, 2022</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/september/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/september/</guid>
      <description>1882: Nietzsche tears through the heavenly veil to find the Body of God, dead for 300 years. The corpse was rotting; maggot demons crawled through all His divine orifices, and the blood from the wound made centuries ago continued to gush forth, invisible to the naked eye, pouring like a monsoon on the realm of the demiurge, drowning all of humanity in ordained monadity.&#xA;C. 50: The remaining druids secretly gather in the Scottish Hills to perform a final ritual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fragment 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/frag1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/frag1/</guid>
      <description>Then was reckoning,&#xA;In the still and hollow night We saw stray cats and hooting owls, And from the chords of your guitar A seismic force shook the world.&#xA;Buildings burned; people screamed; regimes collapsed. The smell of blood + fire took my nostrils.&#xA;I fell on my broken knees. A brick split upon my head. Ash clouded my eyes. The unanimous groans of a condemned world Could not drown your voice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magna Carta...Holy Grail</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/flotsam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/flotsam/</guid>
      <description>yellow converse shoes, seinfeld late at night, still, cranes in the sky Don&amp;rsquo;t touch the flotsam.&#xA;mao&amp;rsquo;s hypothesis: everyday is bleak, awaken in spring&amp;hellip; and Don&amp;rsquo;t touch the flotsam</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Osama Bin Laden</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/osama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/poems/posts/osama/</guid>
      <description>When the Nation&amp;rsquo;s day is finally done, And the Rockefellers have no more fun, And the fever finds its source, And the project runs its course: None will weep at America&amp;rsquo;s last breath, When the yoeman-bourgeois reaches its death. If mine&amp;rsquo;s been beaten, enslaved, riddled with strife, Why shouldn&amp;rsquo;t yours end early? You&amp;rsquo;ve had an air conditioner your whole life.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
