<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Short Stories on POEMS4U</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Short Stories on POEMS4U</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/short-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How He Fell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/whenhefell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/whenhefell/</guid>
      <description>Man is in fact at once I and Thou; he can put himself in the place of another,for this reason, that to him his species, his essential nature, and not merely his individuality, is an object of thought.&#xA;—Ludwig Feuerbach&#xA;As the sun counterpoised the heart of darkness, as it nearly always did, and as the midwinter winds endeavored to chase all those unafraid of whatever hides behind shadows back into the safety of quadruple demarcation, Ava reflected on her day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vultures 0</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/vultures0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/vultures0/</guid>
      <description>After Tolstoy 1&#xA;“When my bird was looking at my computer monitor, I thought ‘wooooah, that bird has no idea what he’s looking at.’ And yet, what does the bird do? Does he panic? No, he can’t really panic, he just does the best he can. Is he able to live in a world where he’s so ignorant? Well, he doesn’t really have a choice. Yeah, he can kinda live… usually the bird’s okay, even though he doesn’t understand the world, and he can kinda learn what’s safe and what’s dangerous.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Excerpt from The Transcript of The 3rd Session between Analyst R and Analysand 5, From The Archive of One « Taboo La Rasa. »</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/taboolarasa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/short-stories/posts/taboolarasa/</guid>
      <description>Cela s’est passé comme suit :&#xA;« Q. » « Well, I had sleeping problems for a while. The doctor recommended things like Clonazepam, Ambien, &amp;amp;c., but I thought I would much rather have something natural. So, I began to take melatonin supplements. Only 5 milligrams, about 30 minutes before I went to bed. As a matter of course, I now began to have issues awaking in the morning. The doctor said something like Wellbutrin, which I happily and willfully ignored.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
